question_data = [{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                  "question": "Stevie Wonder;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                  "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
                  "question": "Throughout the entirety of &quot;Dragon Ball Z&quot;, Goku only kills two characters: a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Art",
                  "question": "Venus of Willendorf is one of the earliest works of art, depicting the planets Mars and Venus embrace in the heavens at night.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
                  "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                                                    "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language &quot;Simlish&quot; was The Sims (2000).",
                                                    "correct_answer": "False",
                                                    "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                  "question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                  "question": "Pistons were added to Minecraft in Beta 1.5.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
                  "question": "Snagglepuss was part of the Yogi Yahooies in the 1977 show Scooby&#039;s All-Star Laff-a-Lympics.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                  "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
